♪The evening breeze gently stirs the stars♪
نسيم المساء يحرك النجوم برفق
♪Like you quietly entering my heart♪
♪ مثلك تدخل قلبي بهدوء ♪
♪I wish for time and you to pause♪
♪ أتمنى لك الوقت وأنت تتوقف
♪In this beautiful moment, only you and I ♪
♪ في هذه اللحظة الجميلة أنا وأنت فقط ♪
♪Moonlight accompanies the silhouette of the stars♪
♪ ضوء القمر يصاحب صورة ظلية النجوم
♪Like a romantic encounter♪
♪ مثل لقاء رومانسي ♪
♪I want to hold your hand and cross through dreams♪
♪ اريد ان امسك يدك واجتاز الاحلام ♪
♪Together, let's search for the most beautiful scenery♪
♪ لنبحث معًا عن أجمل المناظر ♪
♪I want to embark on an adventure of love with you♪
♪ أريد أن أخوض في مغامرة حب معك
♪To fulfill the wishes buried deep in my heart with you♪
لتحقيق الرغبات المدفونة في أعماق قلبي معك
♪Your appearance warms up every day♪
♪ يدفئ مظهرك كل يوم ♪
♪I just want to be by your side forever♪
♪ أريد فقط أن أكون بجانبك إلى الأبد ♪
♪Next to you♪
بجانبك ♪
[Mr. Insomnia Waiting for Love]
[السيد.  الأرق في انتظار الحب]
[Episode 1]
[الحلقة 1]
[GAIA Gu Shuqin]
[جايا جو شوكين]
What is wrong?
[غايا قو شوتشين] ما هو الخطأ؟
It happens again.
يحدث مرة أخرى.
Trance caused by long-term insomnia.
نشوة ناتجة عن الأرق طويل الأمد.
It has been tormenting me for more than a year.
لقد كان يعذبني منذ أكثر من عام.
[GAIA Gu Shuqin Yang Zixuan]
[غايا غو شوكين يانغ زيكسوان]
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Damn insomnia.
لعنة الأرق.
I've missed the qualification for the Asian Symphony Orchestra.
لقد فاتني التأهل للأوركسترا السيمفونية الآسيوية.
Will I...
هل سأفعل ...
never be able to go on stage again?
لن تكون قادرًا على الصعود إلى المسرح مرة أخرى؟
The audition in a month...
الاختبار في شهر ...
is my final chance.
هي فرصتي الأخيرة.
I must cure my insomnia.
يجب أن أعالج الأرق.
Volunteer recruitment.
تجنيد المتطوعين.
Insomnia habilitation program.
برنامج تأهيل الأرق.
There is a hope for my insomnia.
هناك أمل في أرق.
I'll register.
سوف أسجل.
Safely arrived.
وصل بسلامة.
Applying for a return.
التقدم بطلب للعودة.
Over.
زيادة.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
The signing ceremony for insomnia volunteers will start.
سيبدأ حفل التوقيع لمتطوعي الأرق.
This is your speech.
هذا كلامك.
[Kerwin Insomnia habilitation program signing ceremony]
[حفل توقيع برنامج تأهيل Kerwin Insomnia]
Arrange it.
رتبها.
I want to join the insomnia habilitation program.
أرغب في الانضمام إلى برنامج تأهيل الأرق.
But Mr. Song.
لكن السيد سونغ.
There're only 20...
هناك 20 فقط ...
sleep aid devices in total.
أجهزة المساعدة على النوم إجمالاً.
Also.
أيضًا.
The signing ceremony is about to start.
حفل التوقيع على وشك أن يبدأ.
Shall you wait for the next batch?
هل تنتظر الدفعة التالية؟
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
I have to cure my insomnia as soon as possible.
لا بد لي من علاج الأرق في أسرع وقت ممكن.
The board of directors has been picking on me.
كان مجلس الإدارة يختارني.
They'll force me to resign if they know...
سوف يجبرونني على الاستقالة إذا علموا ...
I have insomnia.
لدي الأرق.
You must keep this secret.
يجب أن تحافظ على هذا السر.
Understood, Mr. Song.
فهمت ، السيد سونغ.
But the quota for the volunteers is already full.
لكن حصة المتطوعين ممتلئة بالفعل.
Give me the list of the volunteers.
أعطني قائمة المتطوعين.
She has been eliminated.
لقد تم القضاء عليها.
[Kerwin Group insomnia treatment volunteer personal information Lu Entong]
[المعلومات الشخصية لمتطوع علاج الأرق Kerwin Group Lu Entong]
Isn't this my profile?
أليس هذا ملفي الشخصي؟
Why is it here?
لماذا هو هنا؟
[Contract Signing Ceremony]
[حفل توقيع العقد]
[Contract Signing Ceremony - Kerwin —Overcoming Insomnia Together with You]
[حفل توقيع العقد - كيروين - التغلب على الأرق معك]
Welcome to Kerwin Group's signing ceremony.
مرحبًا بكم في حفل توقيع مجموعة كيروين.
Next,
التالي،
we shall invite Kerwin CEO Song Yanxi
سوف ندعو الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة Kerwin Song Yanxi
to give a speech on stage.
لإلقاء خطاب على خشبة المسرح.
Give him a round of applause.
أعطه جولة من التصفيق.
I'm honoured to see everyone
يشرفني أن أرى الجميع
here today.
هنا اليوم.
[Contract Signing Ceremony]
[حفل توقيع العقد]
Enter.
يدخل.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Please present your entry credentials.
يرجى تقديم أوراق اعتماد الدخول الخاصة بك.
Here.
هنا.
You've been eliminated.
لقد تم القضاء عليك.
You cannot enter.
لا يمكنك الدخول.
What?
ماذا؟
[Contract Signing Ceremony - Kerwin —Overcoming Insomnia Together with You]
[حفل توقيع العقد - كيروين - التغلب على الأرق معك]
Two days later,
بعد يومين،
all volunteers who sign the agreement...
كل المتطوعين الذين وقعوا الاتفاقية ...
will proceed to Kerwin's holiday resort...
سوف ننتقل إلى منتجع عطلات Kerwin ...
to experience the group's sleep aid device.
لتجربة جهاز المساعدة على النوم للمجموعة.
Meanwhile,
في أثناء،
the group is also doing its best...
المجموعة أيضا تبذل قصارى جهدها ...
to develop its new...
لتطوير ...
[Banana 3]
[الموز 3]
sleep aid capsule, Banana 3.
كبسولة النوم ، الموز 3.
Please wait and see.
من فضلك انتظر وانظر.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
The effect of Banana 3 is still unstable.
تأثير Banana 3 لا يزال غير مستقر.
Shall I keep it for you?
هل احتفظ بها لك؟
Thank you, Mr. Song for his thrilling speech.
شكرا لك سيد سونغ على خطابه المثير.
Next, we shall have 19 volunteers to sign...
بعد ذلك ، سيكون لدينا 19 متطوعًا للتوقيع ...
the agreement on stage.
الاتفاق على المسرح.
Please.
لو سمحت.
I have severe insomnia.
أنا أعاني من أرق شديد.
This chance is very important to me.
هذه الفرصة مهمة جدا بالنسبة لي.
Why don't you look again?
لماذا لا تنظر مرة أخرى؟
Look again.
انظر مرة أخرى.
You have a lot of crap.
لديك الكثير من الهراء.
Go to the boss if you have a problem.
اذهب إلى الرئيس إذا كانت لديك مشكلة.
Boss?
رئيس؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Rooftop.
على السطح.
Taking a helicopter.
أخذ طائرة هليكوبتر.
The sky is getting dark.
السماء تصبح مظلمة.
He'll fly away unless you hurry.
سوف يطير بعيدا ما لم تسرع.
Enter.
يدخل.
[Kerwin—Overcoming Insomnia Together with You]
[كيروين - التغلب على الأرق معك]
[Contract Signing Ceremony - Kerwin —Overcoming Insomnia Together with You]
[حفل توقيع العقد - كيروين - التغلب على الأرق معك]
Welcome.
مرحباً.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
I don't know if I should say this.
لا أعرف ما إذا كان ينبغي أن أقول هذا.
According to the group's internal staff,
وبحسب الطاقم الداخلي للمجموعة ،
you're desperate for the development of Banana 3...
أنت في حاجة ماسة إلى تطوير Banana 3 ...
because you have insomnia...
لانك تعانى من الارق ...
lately.
مؤخرا.
Kerwin is a company specialised in sleep technology.
Kerwin هي شركة متخصصة في تكنولوجيا النوم.
If the CEO is known to have insomnia...
إذا كان الرئيس التنفيذي معروفاً بأنه يعاني من الأرق ...
If that is the case,
إذا كان هذا هو الحال،
we'll ruin our own brand.
سوف ندمر علامتنا التجارية الخاصة.
Has he left?
هل غادر؟
You revoke an issued qualification.
قمت بإلغاء مؤهل صادر.
What a fraudulent company.
يا لها من شركة احتيالية.
Why should I be eliminated?
لماذا يجب التخلص مني؟
Banana 3.
الموز 3.
Let me sleep here if you're able.
اسمحوا لي أن أنام هنا إذا كنت تستطيع.
It's been a long while since I had a good sleep.
لقد مرت فترة طويلة منذ أن نمت جيدًا.
Why is he standing at the edge?
لماذا يقف على الحافة؟
He wants to jump off.
يريد القفز.
Don't jump.
لا تقفز.
Why am I suddenly so sleepy?
لماذا أشعر بالنعاس فجأة؟
I'm so sleepy.
أنا نعسان للغاية.
It's so comfortable.
إنه مريح للغاية.
Sleep longer.
النوم لفترة أطول.
Wait a second.
انتظر لحظة.
Did I fall asleep?
هل نمت؟
The Sleeping God shows Its power.
يظهر الإله النائم قوته.
[Sleep]
[ينام]
Sleeping God.
الله النائم.
Bless me with a good sleep.
باركني بنوم جيد.
Thank you, Sleeping God.
شكرا لك يا رب النوم.
Luckily he is fine.
لحسن الحظ انه بخير
He looks quite handsome.
إنه يبدو وسيمًا جدًا.
What bothered him?
ما الذي أزعجه؟
He wanted to jump off the building.
أراد القفز من المبنى.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
[Mr. Song]
[السيد.  أغنية]
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I...
أنا...
Don't bother who I am.
لا تهتم بما أنا عليه.
Hurry and pick him up
اسرع واصطحبه
on the rooftop of Kerwin Tower.
على سطح برج كيروين.
[Banana 3]
[الموز 3]
Why is he on the rooftop?
لماذا هو على السطح؟
He should've taken some pills.
كان يجب أن يأخذ بعض الحبوب.
He is still unconscious.
لا يزال فاقدًا للوعي.
What?
ماذا؟
Stay where you are.
ابق حيث أنت.
I'll be right there.
سأكون هناك.
Oh no!
أوه لا!
I'm supposed to see the doctor with Chi Zuo at 9am.
من المفترض أن أرى الطبيب مع تشي زو في التاسعة صباحًا.
I won't make it for sure.
لن أتأكد من ذلك.
What to do if he wants...
ماذا تفعل إذا أراد ...
to kill himself again after I leave?
لقتل نفسه مرة أخرى بعد أن أغادر؟
I'm doomed.
أنا محكوم عليه بالفشل.
I'll be scolded again.
سأوبخ مرة أخرى.
Morning, Chi Zuo.
صباح الخير ، تشي زو.
Lu Entong.
لو إنتونج.
Do you know how hard I made an appointment...
هل تعرف مدى صعوبة تحديد موعد ...
with the insomnia specialist through my social network?
مع اختصاصي الأرق عبر شبكتي الاجتماعية؟
Look at you.
انظر لحالك.
How late are you?
الى متى انت
He left somewhile ago.
لقد غادر منذ فترة.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I overslept.
نمت كثيرا.
You overslept?
أنت نمت كثيرا؟
You?
أنت؟
You've even learned to lie.
لقد تعلمت الكذب حتى.
It's good enough that you can fall asleep...
من الجيد أن تغفو ...
and yet you oversleep.
ومع ذلك أنت تفرط في النوم.
I'm not lying.
انا لا اكذب.
I really overslept.
أنا حقا نمت.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll make a new appointment with the specialist for you.
سأحدد لك موعدًا جديدًا مع المختص.
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
My Sleeping God showed Its power.
أظهر إلهي النائم قوته.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Whatever you say.
أيا كان ما تقوله.
But you should be on time...
لكن يجب أن تكون في الوقت المحدد ...
for the next appointment.
للموعد القادم.
Fine.
بخير.
Forget it if you don't believe me.
انسى الأمر إذا كنت لا تصدقني.
I'm late today.
لقد تأخرت اليوم.
I'll do all the chores...
سأقوم بكل الأعمال المنزلية ...
in the shop.
في المحل.
Let me.
دعني.
Mercy.
رحمة.
You've broken...
لقد كسرت ...
more cups than the number of my customers.
أكواب أكثر من عدد زبائني.
I'll do it.
سأفعل ذلك.
Chi Zuo.
تشي زو.
Believe me.
ثق بي.
The Sleeping God really showed Its power.
أظهر الله النائم قوته حقًا.
I believe you.
واعتقد انكم.
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
Do you believe I can still sleep tonight?
هل تعتقد أنه لا يزال بإمكاني النوم الليلة؟
That is awesome.
هذا رائع.
Slow down, Mr. Song.
تمهل يا سيد سونغ.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
I'll be fired...
سأطرد ...
if Ms. Chen
إذا السيدة تشين
knows you drive.
يعرف أنك تقود.
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
My insomnia is cured.
تم علاج أرقى.
You're serious, right?
أنت جاد ، صحيح؟
Banana 3 took effect.
دخل الموز 3 حيز التنفيذ.
That is great news.
هذا خبر عظيم.
You don't need these sunglasses anymore then?
لست بحاجة إلى هذه النظارات الشمسية بعد الآن؟
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
However, Mr. Song.
ومع ذلك ، السيد سونغ.
Why did...
لماذا فعلت...
the girl tie you up?
الفتاة تربطك؟
She is just a crazy person.
إنها مجرد شخص مجنون.
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
Hold tight.
تمسك جيدا.
Do you believe I can still sleep tonight?
هل تعتقد أنه لا يزال بإمكاني النوم الليلة؟
I do.
أفعل.
Slow down, Mr. Song.
تمهل يا سيد سونغ.
Sleeping God.
الله النائم.
The chocolate is very delicious.
الشوكولاته لذيذة جدا.
Let me continue...
اسمحوا لي أن أكمل ...
a good sleep tonight.
نوم جيد الليلة.
Please.
لو سمحت.
[Banana 3]
[الموز 3]
Banana 3.
الموز 3.
I count on you tonight.
أنا أعتمد عليك الليلة.
[Sleep]
[ينام]
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Good morning, Mr. Song.
صباح الخير سيد سونغ.
It seems...
يبدو...
you had a good sleep yesterday.
لقد نمت جيدا بالأمس.
Return the sunglasses.
أعد النظارات الشمسية.
[Sleep]
[ينام]
You didn't help...
أنت لم تساعد ...
after receiving the gift from me.
بعد استلام الهدية مني.
[Sleep]
[ينام]
No way.
مستحيل.
I can't go on like this.
لا يمكنني الاستمرار على هذا المنوال.
I must cure my insomnia.
يجب أن أعالج الأرق.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
Your wrist.
معصمك.
It seems that the effect of Banana 3 is still unstable.
يبدو أن تأثير Banana 3 لا يزال غير مستقر.
I have to go to the holiday resort in person...
لا بد لي من الذهاب إلى منتجع العطلات شخصيًا ...
to test the sleep aid device.
لاختبار جهاز المساعدة على النوم.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'll drive you there.
سوف أقودك إلى هناك.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
The volunteers will go to the holiday resort today.
سيذهب المتطوعون إلى منتجع العطلات اليوم.
I'm using the quota of volunteers.
أنا أستخدم حصة المتطوعين.
I'll depart with them by the bus.
سأغادر معهم بالحافلة.
But...
لكن...
they all are insomnia patients...
كلهم مرضى الأرق ...
on the bus.
في الحافلة.
If they recognise you...
إذا تعرفوا عليك ...
as the CEO of Kerwin...
كرئيس تنفيذي لشركة Kerwin ...
Well...
حسنًا...
Give me your jacket.
أعطني سترتك.
I'll inform Huang Lin...
سأخبر هوانغ لين ...
to arrange the reception at the holiday resort.
لترتيب حفل الاستقبال في منتجع العطلات.
Okay.
تمام.
I must pass the audition of the orchestra.
يجب أن أجتاز اختبار الأوركسترا.
[Kerwin Group insomnia treatment volunteer personal information Lu Entong]
[المعلومات الشخصية لمتطوع علاج الأرق Kerwin Group Lu Entong]
I won't simply let go...
لن أتركها ببساطة ...
of this habilitation program.
من برنامج التأهيل هذا.
Please.
لو سمحت.
I have severe insomnia.
أنا أعاني من أرق شديد.
This chance is very important to me.
هذه الفرصة مهمة جدا بالنسبة لي.
Why don't you look again?
لماذا لا تنظر مرة أخرى؟
Look again.
انظر مرة أخرى.
You have a lot of crap.
لديك الكثير من الهراء.
Not the gentle way.
ليس الطريق اللطيف.
I'll take the hard way.
سآخذ الطريق الصعب.
The bus for the insomnia volunteers will depart later.
ستغادر حافلة متطوعي الأرق في وقت لاحق.
I must find a way to sneak onto the bus...
يجب أن أجد طريقة للتسلل إلى الحافلة ...
and join the habilitation program.
والانضمام إلى برنامج التأهيل.
Cure my insomnia thoroughly.
يعالج الأرق تمامًا.
Please present your certificate.
يرجى تقديم شهادتك.
Yes!
نعم!
I'm just in time.
أنا فقط في الوقت المناسب.
Please present your certificate.
يرجى تقديم شهادتك.
Oh no!
أوه لا!
It's the same security guard again.
إنه نفس حارس الأمن مرة أخرى.
Lu Entong.
لو إنتونج.
You must stay tough.
يجب أن تظل قاسياً.
Where is your certificate?
اين شهادتك
[Kerwin Group]
[مجموعة كيروين]
[Kerwin]
[كيروين]
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Aren't you...
ألست أنت ...
You have the wrong person.
لديك الشخص الخطأ.
The bus is about to depart.
الحافلة على وشك المغادرة.
Sit down, passenger at the back.
اجلس ، راكب في الخلف.
Can I take...
هل يمكننى ان اخذ...
this seat?
هذا المقعد؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Please tuck your feet in.
من فضلك ضع قدمك في الداخل.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
He...
هو...
turns out to be also an insomnia patient.
تبين أنه أيضًا مريض بالأرق.
She won't recognise me, right?
انها لن تتعرف علي ، أليس كذلك؟
His wrist is wounded.
معصمه مجروح.
Did he try to cut his wrist a failed jump?
هل حاول قطع معصمه في قفزة فاشلة؟
I'll try to talk to him.
سأحاول التحدث معه.
See if I could comfort him.
انظر إذا كان بإمكاني مواساته.
Do you have insomnia too?
هل تعانين من الأرق أيضًا؟
Life...
حياة...
may not be too nice...
قد لا يكون لطيفًا جدًا ...
but it's definitely not as bad as you think.
لكنها بالتأكيد ليست سيئة كما تعتقد.
Insomnia...
أرق...
isn't a terminal disease.
ليس مرض عضال.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
you've joined the program.
لقد انضممت إلى البرنامج.
Why is this girl so talkative?
لماذا هذه الفتاة ثرثارة جدا؟
He is so autistic.
هو متوحد جدا.
I can't enlighten him...
لا أستطيع أن أنوره ...
when he doesn't talk.
عندما لا يتكلم.
Let's play a game.
لنلعب لعبة.
Pick a guess.
اختر تخمينًا.
Which is my middle finger?
ما هو إصبعي الأوسط؟
Can you be quiet for a moment?
هل يمكنك الهدوء للحظة؟
I'll be quiet if you guess it right.
سأكون هادئًا إذا كنت تخمنها بشكل صحيح.
This one.
هذا.
[Kerwin Resort - Good Sleep Journey]
[منتجع كيروين - رحلة نوم جيدة]
We've arrived.
لقد وصلنا.
Bring your own luggage and belonging.
أحضر أمتعتك وانتمائك.
Get off the bus safely.
النزول من الحافلة بأمان.
Did I fall asleep?
هل نمت؟
Could it be the delayed effect of Banana 3?
هل يمكن أن يكون التأثير المتأخر لـ Banana 3؟
You still volunteer yourself when you can sleep so well.
ما زلت تتطوع بنفسك عندما يمكنك النوم جيدًا.
You should've been eliminated.
كان يجب القضاء عليك.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
This is your room card.
هذه بطاقة غرفتك.
You'll be staying in the room of Volunteer 20.
ستقيم في غرفة المتطوع 20.
Dry clean it.
تنظيفه جافًا.
I'll walk around.
سوف أتجول.
No need to come with me.
لا حاجة للمجيء معي.
Noted.
ذُكر.
Ms. Passenger.
السيدة باسنجر.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
We've arrived.
لقد وصلنا.
We've arrived at the holiday resort.
لقد وصلنا إلى منتجع العطلات.
Get off the bus.
اخرج من الحافلة.
Did I sleep again?
هل أنام مرة أخرى؟
Does the Sleeping God show Its power again?
هل يظهر الإله النائم قوته مرة أخرى؟
Bless me.
باركني.
Let me cure insomnia thoroughly here.
اسمحوا لي أن أعالج الأرق تمامًا هنا.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
Mr. Zhao.
السيد تشاو.
How long does the sleeping aid...
كم من الوقت تساعد النوم ...
of Banana 3 normally take effect?
من الموز 3 ساري المفعول عادة؟
It's unclear yet.
لم يتضح بعد.
Will its effect delay?
هل سيتأخر تأثيره؟
We still have to study more.
لا يزال يتعين علينا دراسة المزيد.
Please come this way.
يرجى تأتي بهذه الطريقة.
Thanks for joining the insomnia habilitation program...
شكرا لانضمامك إلى برنامج تأهيل الأرق ...
in the holiday resort of Kerwin Group.
في منتجع العطلات التابع لمجموعة Kerwin.
This way.
من هنا.
Please collect your room card at the reception with your certificate.
يرجى استلام بطاقة غرفتك في مكتب الاستقبال مع شهادتك.
What to do?
ما يجب القيام به؟
They want to check the certificate again.
يريدون التحقق من الشهادة مرة أخرى.
[Qualification Certificate] Every room of the volunteers...
[شهادة تأهيل] كل غرفة للمتطوعين ...
has a set of sleeping aid.
لديه مجموعة من مساعدات النوم.
Please use it at ease.
الرجاء استخدامه بسهولة.
Shall I discuss with this girl?
هل أناقش هذه الفتاة؟
See if we could stay together.
انظر إذا كان بإمكاننا البقاء معًا.
I just want to know...
انا فقط اريد ان اعرف...
how long the medicine takes effect.
ما هي مدة سريان الدواء.
I've been waiting for long.
كنت انتظر طويلا.
I don't want to wait anymore.
لا أريد الانتظار بعد الآن.
How long will the medicine take effect?
ما هي مدة سريان الدواء؟
He still wants to kill himself.
لا يزال يريد قتل نفسه.
[Kerwin 3rd Floor - Swimming Pool, 2nd Floor - Sleep Aid Room, Technology Room]
[الطابق الثالث من كيروين - حمام السباحة ، الطابق الثاني - غرفة المساعدة على النوم ، غرفة التكنولوجيا]
It's a swimming pool on the third floor.
إنه حمام سباحة في الطابق الثالث.
Does he want to drown himself after taking the medicine?
هل يريد أن يغرق نفسه بعد تناول الدواء؟
[Kerwin 3rd Floor - Swimming Pool, 2nd Floor - Sleep Aid Room, Technology Room]
[الطابق الثالث من كيروين - حمام السباحة ، الطابق الثاني - غرفة المساعدة على النوم ، غرفة التكنولوجيا]
What is going on?
ما الذي يجري؟
There was no delay two days ago.
لم يكن هناك تأخير قبل يومين.
[Swimming Pool]
[حمام السباحة]
[Kerwin Resort - Swimming Pool]
[منتجع كيروين - حمام السباحة]
Why is it her again?
لماذا هي هي مرة أخرى؟
I'm suddenly so sleepy.
فجأة أشعر بالنعاس.
Seriously?
بجد؟
Why do I feel sleepy here?
لماذا أشعر بالنعاس هنا؟
It's not the time to sleep.
إنه ليس وقت النوم.
He can't hold it anymore.
لا يمكنه الاحتفاظ بها بعد الآن.
I cannot sleep now.
لا أستطيع النوم الآن.
I have to save him.
يجب أن أنقذه.
How did I fall asleep?
كيف نمت؟
I didn't take the medicine just now.
لم أتناول الدواء الآن.
Why did I feel sleepy whenever I met him?
لماذا شعرت بالنعاس كلما التقيت به؟
♪Trying to break free♪
♪ تحاول التحرر ♪
♪Pretending to be more carefree than you♪
التظاهر بأنك أكثر راحة منك
♪Simply close my eyes♪
♪ ببساطة أغلق عيني ♪
♪Not looking at the me of the past♪
♪ لا تنظر إلي من الماضي ♪
♪Until it's hard to distinguish♪
حتى يصعب التمييز ♪
♪Loving you is like a game♪
حبك مثل لعبة
♪Deceiving time♪
وقت الخداع
♪Can't deceive myself♪
♪ لا أستطيع خداع نفسي ♪
♪I think I will understand♪
♪ أعتقد أنني سأفهم ♪
♪Won't rely on anyone anymore♪
♪ لن أعتمد على أي شخص بعد الآن ♪
♪Can only exist in memories♪
يمكن أن توجد فقط في الذكريات ♪
♪Drawing the one who loved me - you♪
رسم من أحبني - أنت ♪
♪This farewell is too much of a farce♪
هذا الوداع كثير جدًا من المهزلة
♪No words for parting♪
♪ لا كلام عن الفراق ♪
♪The person who is weak in love isn't me♪
♪ الشخص الضعيف في الحب ليس أنا
♪It's you♪
♪ أنت